Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Books Illustrated and/or Authored by Leonard Everett Fisher ,undated, 1927-1999
  - Letters From Italy, 1977
    - Photocopy of manuscript, undated (Box 26:787)
  - The Death of Evening Star, 1972
    - Notes, undated (Box 26:788)
    - Book proposal, undated (Box 26:789)
    - Crew lists (characters), undated (Box 26:790)
    - Illustration notes / plans, undated (Box 26:791)
    - Illustrations- sketches on parchment, undated (Box 26:792)
    - Glossary, undated (Box 26:793)
    - Manuscript #1 of 3, undated (Box 26:794)
    - Manuscript #2 of 3, undated (Box 26:795)
    - Manuscript #3 of 3, undated (Box 26:796)
    - Font samples, 1971 (Box 26:797)
    - Jacket Flap, undated (Box 26:798)
    - Scratchboard illustration, 1972 (Box 53:1465)
  - Across the Sea from Galway
    - Notes, undated (Box 26:799)
    - Manuscript (complete), undated (Box 26:800)
    - Page drafts, undated (Box 26:801)
  - Snowbound
    - Illustration notes, September 27 (Box 27:802)
    - Map notes, undated (Box 27:803)
    - Maps (5), undated (Box 27:804)
    - Index #1 of 2, undated (Box 27:805)
    - Index (revised) #2 of 2, undated (Box 27:806)
    - Galley, 1995 August 10 (Box 27:807)
    - Correspondence, 1995 June (Box 27:808)
    - Original maps, 1996 (Box 39:1210)
  - The Statue of Liberty, 1985
    - Notes, undated (Box 27:809)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 27:810)
    - Manuscript- first draft, 19085 April (Box 27:811)
    - Manuscript draft #2 of 3, undated (Box 27:812)
    - Manuscript- final draft, 1985 May 2 (Box 27:813)
    - Index draft, undated (Box 27:814)
    - Photo captions- draft, undated (Box 27:815)
    - Photo captions proof #1 of 2, 1985 June 27 (Box 27:816)
    - Photo captions draft #2 of 2, 1985 June 27 (Box 27:817)
    - Index proof #1 of 2, 1985 June 25 (Box 27:818)
    - Index proof #2 of 2, 1985 June 27 (Box 27:819)
    - Galley #1 and 2 of 4, 1985 May 9 (Box 27:820)
    - Galley 3 of 4, 1985 May 9 (Box 27:821)
    - Galley 4 of 4, 1985 June 26 (Box 27:822)
    - Dummy, 1985 (Box 27:823)
    - Book jacket specifications, undated (Box 27:824)
    - Unbound book, 1985 (Box 27:825)
    - Correspondence, 1985 January - May (Box 27:826)
    - Scratchboard illustrations (6), undated (Box 47:1423)
  - Greek Myths [Unpublished]
    - Book plan, undated (Box 28:827)
    - Illustration sketches/ plan, undated (Box 28:828)
    - Timeline (sketch), undated (Box 28:829)
    - Manuscript draft #1, undated (Box 28:830)
    - Draft of introduction with editor's notes, undated (Box 28:831)
    - Manuscript draft #2, undated (Box 28:832)
    - Draft with editor's notes, undated (Box 28:833)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 28:834)
    - Acrylic illustrations (17), 1984 (Box 48:1432)
  - A Head Full of Hats, 1962
    - Proof (Box 28:835)
  - Look Around, 1987
    - Illustration plan / notes, undated (Box 28:836)
    - Acrylic illustrations (11 items), undated (Box 28:837)
    - Acrylic illustrations (4 items), undated (Box 28:838)
    - First draft, 1986 March 3 (Box 28:839)
    - Manuscript draft 2 of 8, 1986 March 10 (Box 28:840)
    - Manuscript draft 3 of 8, undated (Box 28:841)
    - Manuscript draft 4 (incomplete) of 8, undated (Box 28:842)
    - Manuscript draft 5 of 8, undated (Box 28:843)
    - Manuscript draft 6 (revised) of 8, undated (Box 28:844)
    - Manuscript draft 7 of 8, 1986 July (Box 28:845)
    - Manuscript draft 8 of 8, 1986 July 29 (Box 28:846)
    - Black & white photocopies of 4 illustrations, undated (Box 28:847)
    - Book mock-up (photocopy) illustrations only, 1986 April (Box 28:848)
    - Book mock-up (photocopy), undated (Box 28:849)
    - Color specifications, undated (Box 28:850)
    - Book mock-up, undated (Box 28:851)
    - 2 unbound books, 1987 (Box 28:852)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 28:853)
    - Book mock-up, undated (Box 47:1424)
  - Pumpers, Boilers, Hooks & Ladders, 1961
    - Proof, undated (Box 28:854)
  - Pushers, Spads, Jennies & Jets, 1961
    - Proof, undated (Box 28:855)
  - Cyclops, 1991
    - Book plan / notes, undated (Box 29:856)
    - Draft 1, 1990 October 2 (Box 29:857)
    - Draft 2, 1990 December 1 (Box 29:858)
    - Draft 3, 1990 December 12 (Box 29:859)
    - Galley Proof 1 of 4, 1991 January 2 (Box 29:860)
    - Galley 2 (incomplete) of 4, 1991 March 5 (Box 29:861)
    - Galley 3 (incomplete) of 4, 1991 March 6 (Box 29:862)
    - Galley 4 (incomplete) of 4, 1991 March 11 (Box 29:863)
    - Dummy, 1991 (Box 29:864)
    - Correspondence / FedEx slips, 1990-1991 (Box 29:865)
    - Unbound book, 1991 (Box 29:866)
  - The Three Princes, 1994
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 29:867)
    - Illustration sketches, undated (Box 29:868)
    - Unedited manuscript, undated (Box 29:869)
    - Type settings, 1993 August (Box 29:870)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 29:871)
  - The Spotted Pony
    - Acrylic jacket illustration, undated (Box 29:872)
    - Photocopy of jacket illustration (unused), undated (Box 29:873)
    - Jacket specifications, 1992 May 27 (Box 29:874)
    - Photocopy of illustrations, 1992 (Box 29:875)
    - Final manuscript, undated (Box 29:876)
    - Unbound book, 1992 (Box 29:877)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 29:878)
  - Monsieur Jolicoeur's Umbrella
    - Draft, 1966 (Box 29:879)
    - Jacket sketches, undated (Box 29:880)
    - Notes- book production, color sample, undated (Box 29:881)
    - Draft of background information, undated (Box 29:882)
    - Galley (reverse) and 2 pp.'s regular galley, 1967 (Box 29:883)
    - Illustration (color test) from book, undated (Box 29:884)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 29:885)
  - Little Frog's Song, 1992
    - Illustration sketch, undated (Box 29:886)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 29:887)
    - Font test, undated (Box 29:888)
    - Dummy #1, 1991 (Box 29:889)
    - Revised dummy, undated (Box 29:890)
    - Dummy (photocopy), 1991 (Box 29:891)
    - Second proofs, 1991 (Box 29:892)
    - Second proofs, 1991 (Box 29:893)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 29:894)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 38:1208)
  - Celebrations, 1985
    - Book plan/ notes, undated (Box 30:895)
    - Draft with illustration layouts, undated (Box 30:896)
    - Flap copy, undated (Box 30:897)
    - Galley, 1984 (Box 30:898)
    - Proof, undated (Box 30:899)
    - Acrylic illustration (1) unused, 1984 (Box 44:1386)
  - A Circle of Seasons, 1982
    - Book plan/ illustration notes, undated (Box 30:900)
    - Acrylic illustration, undated (Box 30:901)
    - Draft 1 of 2, undated (Box 30:902)
    - Draft 2 of 2, undated (Box 30:903)
    - First Proof, 1981 (Box 30:904)
    - Flap copy, undated (Box 30:905)
    - F & G, 1982 (Box 30:906)
    - Proof-publisher's book blurb, undated (Box 30:907)
    - Proof, undated (Box 30:908)
    - Unbound book, 1982 (Box 30:909)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 30:910)
    - Prospectus, 1982 (Box 30:911)
    - Holiday card, 1982 (Box 30:912)
  - Earth Songs, 1986
    - Draft 1 of 1, undated (Box 30:913)
    - Galley, 1985 (Box 30:914)
    - F & G, 1985 (Box 30:915)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 30:916)
    - Acrylic illustrations (5), 1986 (Box 44:1390)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 44:1391)
  - Festivals
    - Book proposal/ plan, undated (Box 30:917)
    - Notes, undated (Box 30:918)
    - Manuscript draft 1 of 2, undated (Box 30:919)
    - Manuscript draft 2 of 2, undated (Box 30:920)
    - Font test, 1995 August 15 (Box 30:921)
    - Book dummy, blue color separations, 1996 (Box 30:922)
    - Book and jacket dummy, 1996undated (Box 30:923)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 30:924)
    - Photo overlays, undated (Box 38:1204)
    - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 38:1205)
    - Off-set proofs, undated (Box 38:1206)
  - Sea Songs, 1991
    - Draft 1 (revised) of 2, undated (Box 30:925)
    - Draft # 2, undated (Box 30:926)
    - F & G, undated (Box 30:927)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 30:928)
    - Acrylic illustrations (4), 1985 (Box 44:1389)
  - Sky Songs
    - Draft 1 of 2, undated (Box 30:929)
    - Draft 2, undated (Box 30:930)
    - Illustration notes, 1983 (Box 30:931)
    - Photo overlay, undated (Box 30:932)
    - Galley, 1984 (Box 30:933)
    - Original Illustration-Acrylic, 1983 (Box 30:934)
    - F & G, 1984 (Box 30:935)
    - Proof, undated (Box 30:936)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 30:937)
    - Acrylic illustrations (4), 1983 (Box 44:1395)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 44:1396)
  - Space Songs, 1991
    - Draft 1 of 1, undated (Box 30:938)
    - Galley, 1987 (Box 30:939)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 30:940)
    - F & G, 1987 (Box 44:1392)
    - Over-sized book, signed by LEF, 1991 (Box 44:1393)
    - Acrylic illustrations (5), 1987 (Box 44:1394)
  - Up in the Air
    - Draft 1, 1988 (Box 30:941)
    - Draft 2, undated (Box 30:942)
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 30:943)
    - Galleys, 1989 (Box 30:944)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 30:945)
    - Over-sized book, 1989 (Box 44:1387)
  - If You Ever Meet A Whale
    - Manuscript drafts, 1990 (Box 30:946)
    - Book layout, 1991 October (Box 30:047)
    - Book specifications, 1991 (Box 30:948)
    - Type samples, 1991 September (Box 30:949)
    - Dummy, 1991 (Box 30:950)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 30:951)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 44:1388)
  - The Alamo
    - Notes, undated (Box 31:952)
    - Original map illustration, 1986 (Box 31:953)
  - Remington and Russel
    - Notes, undated (Box 31:954)
    - List of paintings, undated (Box 31:955)
    - First draft, undated (Box 31:956)
    - Second draft, undated (Box 31:957)
    - Third draft, undated (Box 31:958)
    - Drafts of pages 1-5, 7-10, undated (Box 31:959)
    - Drafts of pages 11-16, 21-25, 27-28, undated (Box 31:960)
    - Drafts of pages 30-31, 33, undated (Box 31:961)
    - Manuscript-complete, 1985 (Box 31:962)
    - Photocopy of statue, undated (Box 31:963)
  - A Russian Farewell
    - Notes, undated (Box 31:964)
    - First draft (incomplete), undated (Box 31:965)
    - Drafts of author's note, 1978-1979 (Box 31:966)
    - Drafts of pages 1-10, undated (Box 31:967)
    - Drafts of pages 11-20, undated (Box 31:968)
    - Drafts of pages 21-24, 30-34, 37, 39-43, 47-50, undated (Box 31:969)
    - Drafts of pps. 51, 53-57, 61, 64, 66-71, 73-76,79-80, undated (Box 31:970)
    - Drafts of pps. 82, 84, 86-92, 96, 98, undated (Box 31:971)
    - "Second" draft (incomplete), undated (Box 31:972)
    - Completed draft, 1978 (Box 31:973)
  - Sweeney's Ghost
    - Notes, undated (Box 31:974)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 1-2, undated (Box 31:975)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 3-11, undated (Box 31:976)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 13-19, undated (Box 31:977)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 20-end, undated (Box 31:978)
    - Manuscript- complete, 1974 (Box 31:979)
  - The Warlock of Westfall
    - Notes, undated (Box 31:980)
    - Book plan / synopsis, undated (Box 31:981)
    - Jacket sketch, undated (Box 31:982)
    - Manuscript drafts page 1, undated (Box 31:983)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 2-4, undated (Box 31:984)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 5-6, undated (Box 31:985)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 7-8, 10-11, undated (Box 31:986)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 16-19, 21, 26-27, 33, 45, undated (Box 31:987)
    - Manuscript drafts of ending (no page numbers), undated (Box 31:988)
    - Manuscript drafts pages 58, 60, 64, 66, undated (Box 31:989)
    - Manuscript-complete, 1973 (Box 31:990)
    - Book mock-up, undated (Box 39:1212)
    - Scratchboard illustrations (4 items), 1973 (Box 39:1213)
    - Photo overlay, undated (Box 39:1214)
  - Our Presidents
    - Additional president manuscripts to original, undated (Box 32:991)
    - Notes, undated (Box 32:992)
    - Illustration "Washington Crossing the Delaware", undated (Box 32:993)
    - Illustration "John Adams", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:994)
    - Illustration "Jefferson", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:995)
    - Illustration "James Madison", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:996)
    - Illustration "Monroe", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:997)
    - Illustration "John Q. Adams", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:998)
    - Illustration "Jackson", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:999)
    - Illustration "Van Buren", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1000)
    - Illustration "William H. Harrison", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1001)
    - Illustration "Tyler", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1002)
    - Illustration "Polk", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1003)
    - Illustration "Taylor", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1004)
    - Illustration "Fillmore", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1005)
    - Illustration "Pierce", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1006)
    - Illustration "Buchanan", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1007)
    - Illustration "Lincoln", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1008)
    - Illustration "Johnson", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1009)
    - Illustration "Grant", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1010)
    - Illustration "Hayes", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1011)
    - Illustration "Garfield", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1012)
    - Illustration "Arthur", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1013)
    - Illustration "Cleveland", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1014)
    - Illustration "Benjamin Harrison", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:105)
    - Illustration "McKinley", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1016)
    - Illustration "T. Roosevelt", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1017)
    - Illustration "Taft", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1018)
    - Illustration "Wilson", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1019)
    - Illustration "Harding", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1020)
    - Illustration "Coolidge", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1021)
    - Illustration "Hoover", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1022)
    - Illustration "F.D. Roosevelt", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1023)
    - Illustration "Truman", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1024)
    - Illustration "Eisenhower", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1025)
    - Illustration "Kennedy", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1026)
    - Illustration "L.B. Johnson", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1027)
    - Illustration "Nixon", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1028)
    - Illustration "Ford", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1029)
    - Illustration "Carter", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1030)
    - Illustration "Reagan", pen & ink, undated (Box 32:1031)
    - Color seperations of illustrations, undated (Box 32:1032)
    - Proof, undated (Box 32:1033)
    - Jacket proof, undated (Box 50:1437)
  - Picture Book of Revolutionary War Heroes
    - Notes, undated (Box 33:1034)
    - Jacket sketches and color samples, undated (Box 33:1035A)
    - Manuscript drafts of introduction, undated (Box 33:1035)
    - Completed manuscripts Adams-Von Steuben, undated (Box 33:1036)
    - Manuscripts "Ethan Allen", undated (Box 33:1037)
    - Manuscripts "John Adams", undated (Box 33:1038)
    - Manuscripts "Samuel Adams", undated (Box 33:1039)
    - Manuscripts "Captain John Barry", undated (Box 33:1040)
    - Manuscripts "Captain David Bushnell", undated (Box 33:1041)
    - Manuscripts "Henri Christophe", undated (Box 33:1042)
    - Manuscripts "Austin Dabney", undated (Box 33:1043)
    - Manuscripts "Benjamin Franklin", undated (Box 33:1044)
    - Manuscripts "Deborah Gannett", undated (Box 33:1045)
    - Manuscripts "General Horatio Gates", undated (Box 33:1046)
    - Manuscripts "General Nathanael Greene", undated (Box 33:1047)
    - Manuscripts "Nathan Hale", undated (Box 33:1048)
    - Manuscripts "Alexander Hamilton", undated (Box 33:1049)
    - Manuscripts "John Hancock", undated (Box 33:1050)
    - Manuscripts "Mary Ludwig Hays", undated (Box 33:1051)
    - Manuscripts "Edward Hector", undated (Box 33:1052)
    - Manuscripts "Laurens Henry", undated (Box 33:1053)
    - Manuscripts "Patrick Henry", undated (Box 33:1054)
    - Manuscripts "Thomas Jefferson", undated (Box 33:1055)
    - Manuscripts "Captain John Paul Jones", undated (Box 33:1056)
    - Manuscripts "Marquis de Lafayette", undated (Box 33:1057)
    - Manuscripts "Richard Henry Lee", undated (Box 33:1058)
    - Manuscripts "William Livingston", undated (Box 33:1059)
    - Manuscripts "Francis Marion", undated (Box 33:1060)
    - Manuscripts "Saul Mathews", undated (Box 33:1061)
    - Manuscripts "Daniel Morgan", undated (Box 33:1062)
    - Manuscripts "Robert Morris", undated (Box 33:1063)
    - Manuscripts "General William Moultrie", undated (Box 33:1064)
    - Manuscripts "Jeremiah O'Brien", undated (Box 33:1065)
    - Manuscripts "Thomas Paine", undated (Box 33:1066)
    - Manuscripts "Captain John Parker", undated (Box 33:1067)
    - Manuscripts "Andrew Pickens", undated (Box 33:1068)
    - Manuscripts "Colonel William Prescott", undated (Box 33:1069)
    - Manuscripts "Count Casimir Pulaski", undated (Box 33:1070)
    - Manuscripts "General Israel Putnam", undated (Box 33:1071)
    - Manuscripts "Paul Revere", undated (Box 33:1072)
    - Manuscripts "Comte de Rochambeau", undated (Box 33:1073)
    - Manuscripts "Dr. Benjamin Rush", undated (Box 33:1074)
    - Manuscripts "Haym Salomon", undated (Box 33:1075)
    - Manuscripts "Francis Salvador", undated (Box 33:1076)
    - Manuscripts "Jack Sisson", undated (Box 33:1077)
    - Manuscripts "Baron Friedrich Von Steuben", undated (Box 33:1078)
    - Manuscripts "General Thomas Sumtar", undated (Box 33:1079)
    - Manuscripts "General Artemus Ward", undated (Box 33:1080)
    - Manuscripts "Joseph Warren", undated (Box 33:1081)
    - Manuscripts "George Washington", undated (Box 33:1082)
    - Manuscripts "General Anthony Wayne", undated (Box 33:1083)
    - Complete manuscript, 1970 (Box 33:1084)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 33:1085)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (title page), 1970 (Box 34:1086)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (copyright page), 1970 (Box 34:1087)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Introduction), 1970 (Box 34:1088)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (John Adams), 1970 (Box 34:1089)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Samuel Adams), 1970 (Box 34:1090)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Ethan Allen), 1970 (Box 34:1091)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Captain David Bushnell), 1970 (Box 34:1092)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Deborah Gannett), 1970 (Box 34:1093)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Nathanael Green), 1970 (Box 34:1094)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (John Hancock), 1970 (Box 34:1095)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Captain John Parker), 1970 (Box 34:1096)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Colonel William Prescott), 1970 (Box 34:1097)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (General Israel Putnam), 1970 (Box 34:1098)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Paul Revere), 1970 (Box 34:1099)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Jack Sisson), 1970 (Box 34:1100)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (General Artemus Ward), 1970 (Box 34:1101)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Dr. Joseph Warren), 1970 (Box 34:1102)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Captain John Barry), 1970 (Box 34:1103)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Benjamin Franklin), 1970 (Box 34:1104)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Alexander Hamilton), 1970 (Box 34:1105)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Mary Ludwig Hays), 1970 (Box 34:1106)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Edward Hector), 1970 (Box 34:1107)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Captain John Paul Jones), 1970 (Box 34:1108)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (William Livingston), 1970 (Box 34:1109)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (General Daniel Morgan), 1970 (Box 34:1110)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Robert Morris), 1970 (Box 34:1111)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Jeremiah O'Brien), 1970 (Box 34:1112)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Thomas Paine), 1970 (Box 34:1113)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Dr. Benjamin Rush), 1970 (Box 34:1114)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (Haym Salomon), 1970 (Box 34:1115)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (General Philip Schuyler), 1970 (Box 34:1116)
    - Scratchboard paste-up (General Anthony Wayne), 1970 (Box 34:1117)
    - Scratchboard illustration "Nathan Hale"-matted, undated (Box 52:1456)
  - Nineteenth Century America Series
    - Notes / Book plan, undated (Box 35:1118)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 35:1119)
    - The Factories
      - Drafts of page 1, undated (Box 35:1120)
      - Drafts of page 2, undated (Box 35:1121)
      - Drafts of pages 3-7, undated (Box 35:1122)
      - Drafts of pages 8, 10, 12, 13, 16, undated (Box 35:1123)
      - Manuscript, 1979 (Box 35:1124)
      - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 35:1125)
      - Sample unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 35:1126)
    - The Hospitals
      - Manuscript, 1980 (Box 35:1127)
      - Manuscript drafts page 1, undated (Box 35:1128)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 2-6, 8-10, undated (Box 35:1129)
      - 1130 Manuscript drafts pages 11-15, 17-22, 26-29, 31-32, undated (Box 35:1130)
      - Jacket specifications / Illustration, undated (Box 35:1131)
      - Sample unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 35:1132)
      - Dummy, undated (Box 49:1435)
      - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 51:1449)
    - The Newspapers
      - Notes, undated (Box 35:1133)
      - Manuscript drafts, Authors note and page 1, undated (Box 35:1134)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 2-3, undated (Box 35:1135)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 4-32, undated (Box 35:1136)
      - Manuscript (complete) 1 of 2, undated (Box 35:1137)
      - Manuscript 2 of 2, undated (Box 35:1138)
      - Dummy, undated (Box 35:1139)
      - Galley: First proof, 1980 October 22 (Box 35:1140)
      - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 35:1141)
      - Sample unbound book, undated (Box 35:1142)
      - Dummy, undated (Box 49:1436)
      - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 51:1451)
    - The Railroads
      - Manuscript drafts page 1, undated (Box 35:1143)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 2-4, 6, 7, 9-10, undated (Box 35:1144)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 11-20, undated (Box 35:1145)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 22-26, 28-30, 32, undated (Box 35:1146)
      - Manuscript (complete), 1979 (Box 35:1147)
      - F & G, 1979 (Box 35:1148)
      - Jacket specifications, undated (Box 35:1149)
      - Sample unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 35:1150)
      - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 51:1452)
    - The Schools
      - Manuscript, 1983 (Box 36:1151)
      - Master proof, 1982 June 1 (Box 36:1152)
      - Dummy, undated (Box 36:1153)
      - Master proof, 1982 December 2 (Box 36:1154)
      - Unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 36:1155)
      - Photomechanicals, undated (Box 51:1450)
    - The Sports
      - Notes, undated (Box 36:1156)
      - Manuscript, undated (Box 36:1157)
      - Manuscript draft 1 (incomplete), undated (Box 36:1158)
      - Manuscript draft 2 (incomplete), undated (Box 36:1159)
      - Manuscript draft 3 (incomplete), undated (Box 36:1160)
      - Manuscript draft 4 (incomplete), undated (Box 36:1161)
      - Manuscript drafts pages 21 and 5, undated (Box 36:1162)
      - Color swatches, undated (Box 36:1163)
      - Unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 36:1164)
      - Dummy, undated (Box 49:1434)
    - The Unions
      - Manuscript draft, 1982 (Box 36:1165)
      - Dummy, 1982 (Box 36:1166)
      - Unbound book, 1988 December 16 (Box 36:1167)
      - , undated (Box 51:1453)
  - The Art Experience
    - Notes / book plan, undated (Box 37:1168)
    - Draft of author's preface, 1971 (Box 37:1169)
    - Outline / Rough draft, 1970 (Box 37:1170)
    - Draft of Part I: "The First Painter", undated (Box 37:1171)
    - Drafts of Part II and III, undated (Box 37:1172)
    - Drafts of Part IV, undated (Box 37:1173)
    - Author's biography, undated (Box 37:1174)
    - Drafts of glossary, undated (Box 37:1175)
    - Manuscript- complete, undated (Box 37:1176)
    - Complete manuscript w/ editor's notes, 1971 (Box 37:1177)
    - Editor's manuscript, undated (Box 37:1178)
    - Final manuscript revisions, 1971 December 1 (Box 37:1179)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 37:1180)
    - Original illustrations- mixed media (5), 1973 (Box 53:1464)
  - The Art of Leonard Everett Fisher
    - Book plan, undated (Box 37:1181)
    - Materials included / description of paintings, undated (Box 37:1182)